<Texts Type="Thing">
	<List>
		<Text Name="Item_Boss_Jiaowangci" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Wyrm King Horn</ThingName>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Boss_Fenghuangneidan" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>ฟินิกซ์ Core</ThingName>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Boss_Fenghuanghuoyu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>ฟินิกซ์ Flame Feather</ThingName>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossFeng_HuoYu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Blazing Feather</ThingName>
			<Desc>A peculiar feather, although it is not very hot to the touch, it can keep diffusing heat indefinitely, significantly increasing the temperature of a room or other confined space. It doesn't seem to have much use except for its strong spirit converging effect.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Feather</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossFeng_GangYu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>ฟินิกซ์ Ironclad Feather</ThingName>
			<Desc>An intact ฟินิกซ์ feather, its immense heat entirely confined within. It is sharp and sturdy. Wearing it enables one to become impervious to cold, speeding up the circulation of พลังชี่ and blood as well as boosting food consumption rate.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Feather</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossFeng_TouYu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>ฟินิกซ์ Oblivion Feather</ThingName>
			<Desc>The gorgeous feather in eternal flames from ฟินิกซ์'s head, containing its concentrated essence. ฟินิกซ์ is skilled in the ways of spells. Wearing it allows one to harness the power of ฟินิกซ์ and break through the skill limit of Spell by 3 levels.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Feather</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossFeng_WeiYu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>ฟินิกซ์ Mantle Feather</ThingName>
			<Desc>ฟินิกซ์'s huge tail feather. Despite the glowing flame dwelling atop it, one feels moderately warm rather than burning hot upon touching it, which is quite marvelous. It should have some peculiar effects after having been processed with a special method.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Feather</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossFeng_Gu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>ฟินิกซ์ Iron Bone</ThingName>
			<Desc>The hollow bones of ฟินิกซ์'s two wings, they are unusually firm and weightless. It should have some peculiar effects after having been processed with a special method.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Feather</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossFeng_HongYu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>ฟินิกซ์ Fire Jade</ThingName>
			<Desc>ฟินิกซ์'s source of power; this is where its วิญญาณบรรพกาล resides. If one communicate with its วิญญาณบรรพกาล, one might be able to comprehend some useful information from it. Wearing it allows one to harness ฟินิกซ์'s power and take 10% less Fire damage.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>หยก</Item.FabaoSuffix>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Meditate</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to obtain some useful information from it.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossFeng_Meat" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>ฟินิกซ์ Flesh</ThingName>
			<Desc>The finest flesh and blood of ฟินิกซ์'s body, consuming it increase one's ค่าพลังชี่สูงสุด by 25, and extend Lifespan for 10 years. Multiple consumptions will gradually diminish its effect.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Flesh</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_DragonScale" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Dragon Scale</ThingName>
			<Desc>Scale fallen from dragon's body, it has lost most of its magical qualities except for a strong spirit converging effect.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Scale</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossLong_Jiao" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>มังกรหลาก Horn</ThingName>
			<Desc>The horn on top of มังกรหลาก's head, it is where the dragon's essence is concentrated. มังกรหลาก is skilled in the ways of Artifact Mastery. Wearing it allows one to harness the power of มังกรหลาก and break through the skill limit of Sword Mastery by 3 levels.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Thorn</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossLong_Zhua" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>มังกรหลาก Devil Claw</ThingName>
			<Desc>Sharp claw from มังกรหลาก, it has no shortage of sharpened edges and possess unstoppable destructive power. It should have some peculiar effects after having been processed with a special method.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Thorn</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossLong_Lin" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>มังกรหลาก Scale</ThingName>
			<Desc>An intact scale from the body of มังกรหลาก, it is quite indestructible. Wearing it enables one to resist พลังชี่ Damage.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Scale</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossLong_NiLin" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>มังกรหลาก Forbidden Scale</ThingName>
			<Desc>The source of มังกรหลาก's power, this is where its วิญญาณบรรพกาล resides. If one communicate with its วิญญาณบรรพกาล, one might be able to comprehend some useful information from it. Wearing it allows one to harness the power of มังกรหลาก, and take 10% less Water damage.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Scale</Item.FabaoSuffix>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Meditate</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to obtain some useful information from it.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossLong_Jing" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>มังกรหลาก Wrath Vein</ThingName>
			<Desc>The toughest tendon-เส้นพลังชี่ in มังกรหลาก's tail, it is of excellent พลังชี่ conductivity. It should have some peculiar effects after having been processed with a special method.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Tendon</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossLong_Meat" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>มังกรหลาก Flesh</ThingName>
			<Desc>The finest flesh and blood of มังกรหลาก's body, consuming it increase one's ค่าพลังชี่สูงสุด by 25, and extend Lifespan for 10 years. Multiple consumptions will gradually diminish its effect.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Flesh</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossZhuLong_BaiLin" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>White Scale</ThingName>
			<Desc>Pure white scale shed from มังกรประทีป's body.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Scale</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossZhuLong_HeiLin" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Black Scale</ThingName>
			<Desc>Pitch black scale shed from มังกรประทีป's body.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Scale</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossZhuLong_Eye" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Yin-Yang Crystal</ThingName>
			<Desc>Transparent crystals of the mixed black and white colors in มังกรประทีป's eyes, through which one can seemingly decipher the mysteries of the ways of yin and yang. It should have some peculiar effects after having been processed with a special method.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Crystal</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossZhuLong_TianLin" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Divine มังกรประทีป Scale</ThingName>
			<Desc>The odd shaped scale in between the มังกรประทีป's eyebrows, it is where the dragon's essence is concentrated. Five Elements which have been transformed by มังกรประทีป from Yin and Yang. Wearing it allows one to harness the power of มังกรประทีป and break through the skill limit of Barrier by 3 levels.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Scale</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossZhuLong_LongYu" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Chaos Jade</ThingName>
			<Desc>มังกรประทีป's source of power, this is where a wisp of its remaining วิญญาณบรรพกาล resides. If one communicate with its วิญญาณบรรพกาล, one might be able to comprehend some useful information from it. Wearing it allows one to harness the power of มังกรประทีป, and take 5% less elemental damage.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>หยก</Item.FabaoSuffix>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Meditate</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Attempt to obtain some useful information from it.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossZhuLong_Meat" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Primeval Flesh</ThingName>
			<Desc>Blood and flesh from มังกรประทีป's body, it is tainted by the power of Yin and Yang and thus has unique uses. Consuming it decreases ค่าความสำเร็จ by 2 and extends Lifespan by 10 years. Multiple consumptions will gradually diminish its effect.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Flesh</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossFeng_FengYin" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>ฟินิกซ์ Jade</ThingName>
			<Desc>An ancient piece of jade from the treasures of the dragon's platform, it seems to be one of a set of items.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>หยก</Item.FabaoSuffix>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspect</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Inspect the ฟินิกซ์ Jade.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BossZhuLong_FengYin" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>Ancient Jade</ThingName>
			<Desc>A peculiar piece of jade found on the Heavenly Battlefield, the ancient battlefield. The essence of Yin and Yang flickers within it, as if nurturing something.</Desc>
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>หยก</Item.FabaoSuffix>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Inspect</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Inspect the Ancient Jade.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>