<Texts Type="Thing">
	<List>
		<Text Name="RockBase" sParam="Item">
			<Item.FabaoSuffix>Stone, Seal, Stele, Dualjade, Tablet, Tower, Boulder</Item.FabaoSuffix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_BrownRock" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>หินสีน้ำตาล</ThingName>
			<Desc>Stone of a brown color; a very common material.</Desc>
			<Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>หินสีน้ำตาล</Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_GrayRock" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>หินสีเทา</ThingName>
			<Desc>Stone of a grey color; a very common material.</Desc>
			<Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>หินสีเทา</Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Marble" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>หินอ่อน</ThingName>
			<Desc>Marble is a common stone material. Its texture is rather attractive.</Desc>
			<Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>หินอ่อน</Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_Jade" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>หยก</ThingName>
			<Desc>Fine and hard stone that is glossy and slightly translucent, it is very attractive and full of spiritual qualities.</Desc>
			<Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>หยก</Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_JadeEssence" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>แกนหยก</ThingName>
			<Desc>The essence of a jade stone, it is light in weight, has a smooth surface and very beautiful. Often used for making high-end decorations, and also for medicine.</Desc>
			<Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>แกนหยก</Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_StoneEssence" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>แกนหิน</ThingName>
			<Desc>The essence of a stone, it is light in weight, has a smooth surface and very beautiful. Often used for making high-end decorations, and also for medicine.</Desc>
			<Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>แกนหิน</Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_SkyStone" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>หินศักดิ์สิทธิ์</ThingName>
			<Desc>A rare kind of rock said to be dug up from the celestial pillars, with boisterous พลังชี่ of the Earth element dwelling within it.</Desc>
			<Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>หินศักดิ์สิทธิ์</Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_ExtremeJade" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>หินเทพ</ThingName>
			<Desc>A much sought-after treasure among cultivators, it naturally presents the form of a cylindrical crystal. Possesses exceptional พลังชี่ adaptability.</Desc>
			<Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>หินเทพ</Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_LingStone" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>หินวิญญาณ</ThingName>
			<Desc>Solid formed by condensation of highly concentrated พลังชี่. Consuming it restores 500 พลังชี่, and improves your พลังชี่ Affinity for a certain period of time.</Desc>
			<Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>หินวิญญาณ</Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="Item_LingCrystal" sParam="Item">
			<ThingName>คริสตัลวิญญาณ</ThingName>
			<Desc>Crystal formed by condensation of highly concentrated พลังชี่. Consuming it restores 20000 พลังชี่, and significantly improves your พลังชี่ Affinity for a certain period of time.</Desc>
			<Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>คริสตัลวิญญาณ</Item.BeMaterial.NamePrefix>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>