<Texts Type="Thing">
	<List>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Huo" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Fire รากวิญญาณ: ผลไม้แดงสด Tree</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of ผลไม้แดงสด, an ยาแห่งธาตุ. Grows in a place with dense พลังชี่, compatible element and ดินที่อุดมสมบูรณ์. For its special trait, it has to grow in an environment above 200℃.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Jin" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Metal รากวิญญาณ: Sagacity Tree</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of ผลไม้ปราชญ์, an ยาแห่งธาตุ. Grows in a place with dense พลังชี่, compatible element and ดินที่อุดมสมบูรณ์. Extremely sensitive to high temperature, but relatively resistant to cold. It has to grow in an environment below 20℃.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Mu" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Wood รากวิญญาณ: Gnarled Vine</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Gnarled Vine, an ยาแห่งธาตุ. Grows in a place with dense พลังชี่, compatible element and ดินที่อุดมสมบูรณ์. It has a strict requirement for environment temperature, and only grows in between 15-35℃.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Shui" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Water รากวิญญาณ: Prism Lotus</ThingName>
			<Desc>The Prism Lotus plant, an ยาแห่งธาตุ. Grows in places with dense พลังชี่, compatible element and ดินที่อุดมสมบูรณ์. It prefers low temperature, and only grows in an environment below -120℃.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Tu" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Earth รากวิญญาณ: Ocher Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Ocher Essence, an ยาแห่งธาตุ. Grows in a place with dense พลังชี่, compatible element and ดินที่อุดมสมบูรณ์. It avoids low temperature, and only grows in an environment above 30℃.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Huo_ZF" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Fire รากวิญญาณ: ผลไม้แดงสด Tree</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of ผลไม้แดงสด, an ยาแห่งธาตุ. It is said to only grow in places with dense พลังชี่, compatible element and ดินที่อุดมสมบูรณ์.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Examine</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Try to examine it closely with your Perception.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Jin_ZF" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Metal รากวิญญาณ: Sagacity Tree</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Sagacity Fruit, an ยาแห่งธาตุ. It is said to only grow in places with dense พลังชี่, compatible element and ดินที่อุดมสมบูรณ์.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Examine</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Try to examine it closely with your Perception.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Mu_ZF" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Wood รากวิญญาณ: Gnarled Vine</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Gnarled Vine, an ยาแห่งธาตุ. It is said to only grow in places with dense พลังชี่, compatible element and ดินที่อุดมสมบูรณ์.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Examine</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Try to examine it closely with your Perception.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Shui_ZF" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Water รากวิญญาณ: Prism Lotus</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Prismatic Lotus, an ยาแห่งธาตุ. It is said to only grow in places with dense พลังชี่, compatible element and ดินที่อุดมสมบูรณ์.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Examine</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Try to examine it closely with your Perception.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="LingZhi_Tu_ZF" sParam="Plant">
			<ThingName>Earth รากวิญญาณ: Ocher Essence</ThingName>
			<Desc>The plant of Ochre Essence, an ยาแห่งธาตุ. It is said to only grow in places with dense พลังชี่, compatible element and ดินที่อุดมสมบูรณ์.</Desc>
			<StoryBnts.0.Name>Examine</StoryBnts.0.Name>
			<StoryBnts.0.Desc>Try to examine it closely with your Perception.</StoryBnts.0.Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>