<Texts Type="Other">
	<List>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_1_Shui">
			<Title>Comprehend - กฎ 16 ขั้นสูงสุด</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in กฎ 16 ขั้นสูงสุด are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_2_Mu">
			<Title>Comprehend - กฎสมบัติเหลือคณนา</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in กฎสมบัติเหลือคณนา are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_3_Jin">
			<Title>Comprehend - เจ็ดดาบสังหาร</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in เจ็ดดาบสังหาร are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_4_None">
			<Title>Comprehend - Jade Purity เซียน Law</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in Jade Purity เซียน Law are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_5_Tu">
			<Title>Comprehend - กฎขโมยสวรรค์</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in กฎขโมยสวรรค์ are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_6_Huo">
			<Title>Comprehend - กฎเล่นแร่แปลธาตุดึกดำบรรพ์</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in กฎเล่นแร่แปลธาตุดึกดำบรรพ์ are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_7_Huo">
			<Title>Comprehend - กฎสะบั้นอารมณ์</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in กฎสะบั้นอารมณ์ are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_8_Jin">
			<Title>Comprehend - Law of Strife</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in Law of Strife are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_9_Mu">
			<Title>Comprehend - กฎหกอวตาร</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in กฎหกอวตาร are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_10_Huo">
			<Title>Comprehend - กฎกลั่นตะวัน</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in กฎกลั่นตะวัน are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_11_Tu">
			<Title>Comprehend - กฎกลั่นทานตะวัน</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in กฎกลั่นทานตะวัน are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateGong_12_None">
			<Title>Comprehend - Primordial Symbols Law</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in Primordial Symbols Law are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateDengXian">
			<Title>Comprehend - Ascension Law</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in some version of Ascension Law circulated in the world of the travelling warriors are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateYuanShen">
			<Title>Comprehend - กฎวิญญาณบรรพกาล</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in some version of กฎวิญญาณบรรพกาล circulated in the world of the travelling warriors are shown on this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateJinDan">
			<Title>Comprehend - Golden Core Law</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in some version of Golden Core Law circulated in the world of the travelling warriors have are shown this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
		<Text Name="PenetrateFanSu">
			<Title>Comprehend - Worldly Law</Title>
			<Desc>The secret techniques contained in some version of Worldly Law circulated in the world of the travelling warriors have are shown this page.</Desc>
		</Text>
	</List>
</Texts>